hello brothers and sisters this is ey on
ey censored supernal Bible changes on
YouTube and today is Friday February 9th
2024 and I wanted to let you know that
my latest book is available on Amazon
it's called what the Bible says about
money wealth and work Supernatural Bible
changes this particular book it's
5.75 by 6 in so it's small but it has
over
400 King James Bible verses and other
translations primarily King James Bible
like
95% of changes alterations to the King
James Bible related to these topics
we're seeing l signs and wonders happen
right now our bibles are supernaturally
changing and there is a different voice
that's coming through scripture we're
seeing nonsense verses doctrinal errors
emoticons punctuation and grammar errors
new words new people words erased new
titles to various books of the Bible and
on and on it
goes the Bible warned us of this hour
and told us that the that the Antichrist
would come with lying signs and wonders
and there would be a great falling away
do you remember that in 2 Thessalonians
2: 3-1 you need to go read that and
another great passage to read is from
Amos talking about the changing of times
and
laws this is what we're seeing happen
today let me go ahead and show you the
page on Amazon here here it is and this
was released today it has over 400 Bible
verses um filled with new words related
to money wealth and work we now have new
words in the King James Bible like
mortgaged Penny wealthy Bill Financial
Bank uh leasing employment Porters Dukes
Chiefs presidents doctors lawyers town
clerk Pilots sheriffs and many other new
words now plopped into the King James
Bible I know that sounds pretty wild
doesn't it but we're seeing really
Grievous heinous and
blasphemous Bible changes in scripture
today it's an allog together new book
and it's time to wake up in Jesus name
let me go ahead and show you what my
some of these verses are that I've
included this is my
manuscript I put two verses on each
page and here here we go first Kings
10:28 says this today and Solomon had
horses brought out of Egypt and linen
yarn the king's Merchants received the
linen yarn at a
price Jeremiah 4:6 set up the standard
toward Z on
retire stay not for I will bring evil
from the north and a great
destruction 1 Corinthians 5:11 but now I
have written unto you not to keep
Company If any man that is called a
brother be a fornicator or Covetous or
an idolator or a or a drunkard or
an
extortioner with such and one
know not to
eat James 5:7 therefore be patient
Brethren until the coming of the Lord
this is in the new King James Bible by
the way see how the farmer waits for the
precious fruit of the earth waiting
patiently for it until it receives the
early and latter
rain Hebrews 10:23 let us hold fast the
profession of our faith without wavering
for he is faithful that promised with an
emoticon a winky oton
nonetheless Revelations
18:17 for in one hour so great riches is
come to not and every shipmaster and all
the company in ships and sailors and as
many as trade by sea stood a far off
Ezekiel 18:7 and hath not oppressed any
but hath restored to the deor his pledge
hath spoiled none by violence hath given
his bread to the hungry and hath covered
the naked with a
garment Philippians 3:2 beware of
dogs beware of evil
workers Beware of the
concision
two more 1st Samuel 17:18 and carry
these 10
cheeses unto the captain of their
thousand and look how thy Brethren fare
and take their
pledge job 24:3 they drive away the ass
of the fatherless they take the Widow's
Ox for a
pledge these are just a
sample of verses in the this
book of altered scripture verses related
to money wealth and work it's time to
wake up in jesus' name these Bible
changes that we're seeing are self
evident they're obvious for anyone who
has eyes to see and we're
seeing changes on every single page of
the Bible from Genesis to Revelations
and even the preface there's a preface a
new preface in the King James Bible
dedicated to Queen
Elizabeth we have new maps in our Bibles
and on and on it
[Music]
goes I don't know what else to tell you
do your research pray and fast and seek
the
Lord these Chang Es are obvious for
anyone who's been reading
scripture anyone with
discernment we have new and modern words
in the Bible that have no business being
there there's graphic vulgar language
now in
scripture and all types of new words
it's like messaging and there's an
Alchemy going on it's witchcraft sending
curses upon the Earth I've been studying
this topic now
for it will be seven years in June 7
years or actually I take that back eight
years come this June of
2024 it's time to wake up from your
Slumber
Church be strong and courageous brothers
and sisters do not fear or be dismayed
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go until next
time